<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Learning</string>
    <string name="image1_title">Basic coding skills</string>
    <string name="image1_description">Learn basic coding with any language. Use tutorials, practice projects, and ask questions. Focus on understanding concepts rather than memorization.</string>
    <string name="image2_title">Basic graphic design principles</string>
    <string name="image2_description">Learn fundamentals like typography, color theory, and layout. Study examples and practice using design software like Adobe Illustrator or Canva.</string>
    <string name="image3_title">Cooking a new recipe every day</string>
    <string name="image3_description">Experiment with new recipes. Explore diverse cuisines. Practice cooking techniques. Enjoy the process and expand your culinary repertoire.</string>
    <string name="image4_title">Effective time management strategies</string>
    <string name="image4_description">Prioritize tasks. Use calendars and to-do lists. Break tasks into smaller steps. Minimize distractions. Learn to delegate and say no when necessary.</string>
    <string name="image5_title">Gardening basics</string>
    <string name="image5_description">Start with soil preparation and plant selection. Learn about watering, sunlight, and spacing requirements. Begin with easy-to-grow plants like herbs or salad greens.</string>
    <string name="image6_title">Introduction to interior design principles</string>
    <string name="image6_description">Understand principles like balance, harmony, and focal points. Study color schemes and furniture arrangement. Experiment with textures and lighting. Create mood boards for inspiration.</string>
    <string name="image7_title">Introduction to philosophy </string>
    <string name="image7_description">Explore key concepts like ethics, metaphysics, and epistemology. Study influential philosophers and their ideas. Reflect on questions about existence, knowledge, and morality.</string>
    <string name="image8_title">Improving public speaking skills</string>
    <string name="image8_description">Practice regularly with prepared speeches and impromptu talks. Focus on body language, voice modulation, and engaging storytelling. Seek feedback and gradually increase speaking opportunities.</string>
    <string name="image9_title">Basic first aid and CPR training</string>
    <string name="image9_description">Learn to assess and respond to medical emergencies. Understand CPR techniques for adults, children, and infants. Practice bandaging wounds and treating burns.</string>
    <string name="image10_title">Mind mapping and brainstorming techniques</string>
    <string name="image10_description">Start with a central idea. Branch out with related concepts or tasks. Use visuals, colors, and keywords. Encourage free-flowing ideas without judgment.</string>
    <string name="image11_title">Learning to solve Rubik\'s Cube or similar puzzles</string>
    <string name="image11_description">Understand cube notation and basic algorithms. Practice layer-by-layer solving methods. Use online tutorials and apps for guidance. Patience and repetition are key to mastering the solution.</string>
    <string name="image12_title">Introduction to drawing and sketching</string>
    <string name="image12_description">Start with simple shapes and lines. Practice observing and capturing proportions. Learn shading techniques for depth and texture. Experiment with different mediums and subjects.</string>
    <string name="image13_title">Basic car maintenance</string>
    <string name="image13_description">Learn to check fluids (oil, coolant, brake fluid). Understand how to change a tire and jumpstart a car. Perform regular inspections (lights, brakes, tires). Follow the manufacturer\'s maintenance schedule for oil changes and other services.</string>
    <string name="image14_title">Introduction to woodworking</string>
    <string name="image14_description">Start with basic tools like saws, drills, and sanders. Learn safety precautions and proper tool usage. Practice making simple projects like shelves or picture frames. Experiment with different types of wood and joinery techniques.</string>
    <string name="image15_title">Basic electronics</string>
    <string name="image15_description">Understand components like resistors, capacitors, and diodes. Learn to read schematics and circuit diagrams. Practice soldering and breadboarding. Experiment with simple projects like LED circuits or basic amplifiers.</string>
    <string name="image16_title">Developing a daily exercise routine</string>
    <string name="image16_description">Set specific goals (e.g., cardio, strength, flexibility). Start with a warm-up and end with a cool-down. Incorporate varied activities (e.g., walking, yoga, weightlifting). Track progress and adjust intensity gradually.</string>
    <string name="image17_title">Improving your handwriting</string>
    <string name="image17_description">Focus on consistent letter size and spacing. Practice writing slowly and deliberately. Use lined paper or guide sheets. Experiment with different writing utensils and grips.</string>
    <string name="image18_title">Understanding the basics of investing in stocks and bonds</string>
    <string name="image18_description">Learn the difference between stocks (ownership) and bonds (debt). Study concepts like risk, diversification, and returns. Explore how to analyze financial statements and evaluate investment opportunities.</string>
    <string name="image19_title">Learning basic of hunting</string>
    <string name="image19_description">Understand hunting regulations and safety protocols. Learn to identify game species and habitats. Practice shooting and firearm safety. Develop tracking and field dressing skills.</string>
    <string name="image20_title">Learning to play chess and basic strategies</string>
    <string name="image20_description">Familiarize yourself with the board and pieces. Learn how each piece moves. Practice basic opening principles (control the center, develop pieces). Study tactics like forks, pins, and skewers.</string>
    <string name="image21_title">Introduction to cybersecurity</string>
    <string name="image21_description">Understand common threats like malware, phishing, and hacking. Learn to create strong passwords and use encryption. Familiarize yourself with basic network security concepts. Practice safe browsing habits and recognize potential risks.</string>
    <string name="image22_title">Basic video editing skills</string>
    <string name="image22_description">Start with software like iMovie or Adobe Premiere. Learn to import, cut, and arrange clips. Experiment with transitions, effects, and audio enhancements. Practice exporting and sharing your edited videos.</string>
    <string name="image23_title">Understanding the basics of astronomy and stargazing</string>
    <string name="image23_description">Learn about celestial objects like stars, planets, and galaxies. Understand concepts such as orbits, phases, and constellations. Practice stargazing with the naked eye or a telescope. Familiarize yourself with astronomical events and phenomena.</string>
    <string name="image24_title">Basic sewing and mending skills</string>
    <string name="image24_description">Start with hand-sewing techniques like threading a needle and tying knots. Learn basic stitches like straight stitch, backstitch, and whipstitch. Practice mending clothing and simple sewing projects like hemming pants or sewing on buttons.</string>
    <string name="image25_title">Introduction to geology and rock identification</string>
    <string name="image25_description">Understand the basic principles of geology, including rock types, formations, and the rock cycle. Learn to identify common minerals and rocks based on their physical properties such as color, texture, and hardness. Explore geological processes such as erosion, deposition, and plate tectonics. Utilize field guides and online resources to aid in rock identification.</string>
    <string name="image26_title">Basic wilderness survival skills</string>
    <string name="image26_description">Learn shelter-building, water purification, fire-starting, and foraging skills. Study plant identification and basic navigation for wilderness safety and survival.</string>
    <string name="image27_title">Learning basic sign language</string>
    <string name="image27_description">Start with the alphabet and common phrases. Practice finger spelling and basic gestures. Learn everyday vocabulary and simple sentence structures.</string>
    <string name="image28_title">Introduction to beekeeping</string>
    <string name="image28_description">Understand bee anatomy and hive structure. Learn basic equipment and safety measures. Study bee behavior and seasonal hive management. Practice hive inspections and honey extraction techniques.</string>
    <string name="image29_title">Learning to make homemade bread</string>
    <string name="image29_description">Start with simple recipes like white or whole wheat bread. Learn basic techniques such as kneading, proofing, and shaping dough. Experiment with different types of flour and additives.</string>
    <string name="image30_title">Introduction to horseback riding</string>
    <string name="image30_description">Begin with basic horse care and safety procedures. Learn mounting and riding techniques such as posture, rein control, and cues. Practice in a controlled environment under supervision.</string>
    <string name="day">day %d</string>
    <string name="app_bar">30 DAYS OF LEARNING</string>
</resources>